Patrick Carrington

Leamington Spa, Warwickshire www.linkedin.com/in/p-t-carrington

PROFILE

I'm a conscientious and enthusiastic student currently in my final year of my BSc Computing degree. My work experience at Tesco has helped me develop teamwork, communication and leadership skills as well as giving me extensive work experience in retail environment. I enjoy watching Formula One races and Rugby matches and am a keen photographer.

EDUCATION

University of Buckingham – BSc (Hons) Computing

2020-Present

On course for First Class (module average 84%), graduating December 2022

Undergraduate Project: Automatic Detection of Empty Supermarket Shelves

Key Modules Include: Information Security (90%), Web Apps Development (90%), Principles of Computer Networks (87%), Object Oriented Programming (85%), Image Processing (83%), Software Engineering (80%), Analysis, Design & Implementation of Algorithms (80%), Human-Computer Interaction (78%), Principles of Database Systems (74%), Software Project Management (72%)

Friends of the University of Buckingham Prize for Special Achievement at Part 1

Princethorpe College – A Levels

2019

Mathematics, Chemistry, Physics, Extended Project Qualification

Academic Senior Prefect & Science Leader

Princethorpe College - GCSEs

2017

11 GCSEs/IGCSEs A*-C including English & Maths. Latin Level 2 Certificate and Higher Project Qualification

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Assistant (Services & Petrol Filling Station) | Tesco Stores Ltd.

Nov 2017 - Present

Part time job during my A-Levels, Gap Year and University at the Warwick and Buckingham stores in the Cash Office, Customer Service Desk and Petrol Filling Station. Trained in supporting other areas of the store including cover as Service Team Support.

- Serve customers and deal with complaints and sensitive issues in a professional manner
- Use analytical and problem solving skills when investigating shrink and cash discrepancies
- Use an eye for detail and compliance when delivering mock Store Controls and Safe & Legal audits
- Help upskill and train colleagues in the Service areas of the store, ensuring that they fully understand their role and any legal training
- I respond quickly to First Aid incidents, working well under stressful conditions and ensure that reports and next steps are completed promptly

Student Ambassador | University of Buckingham

Aug 2021 - Present

- Communicate with prospective students through the university's 'Chat with a Student' webpage
- Represent the University at Open Days and Taster Events
- Give tours to prospective students/families
- Collaborate with other Ambassadors, the Marketing Team and Faculty Leadership to help provide a good experience to visitors and prospective students

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Camps International Costa Rica – Expedition Volunteer

July - August 2018

I fundraised over £2500 for and completed a four week expedition in Costa Rica contributing to conservation projects and community work.

Education Volunteer – Rainsbrook STC

2018

Along with other Sixth Form students from Princethorpe College, I volunteered at Rainsbrook Secure Training Centre to help teach mathematics to the trainees

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- C++
- Python
- Javascript
- SQL
- HTML/CSS
- MATLAB
- Django
- Microsoft Office

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Level 3 First Aid at Work [2019] Full UK Driving Licence [2019]

References available on request